Are you feeling peckish?
你感觉有点饿吗？
Maybe it's a while until your next meal, so perhaps now you're thinking about reaching for a brightly coloured packet with something delicious inside.
也许离下一顿饭还有一段时间，所以现在你可能正想着伸手去拿一个色彩鲜艳的包装袋，里面装着美味的东西。
Maybe it's time for a snack.
也许是时候吃点零食了。
You're not alone, we all do it – but just how much work goes into developing and making the snacks that we all know and love?
你并不孤单，我们都这样——但开发和生产我们所熟知和喜爱的零食究竟需要多少功夫呢？
First, companies have to work out what people have an appetite for.
首先，公司必须弄清楚人们对什么有食欲。
Traditionally, they might just have asked people about their snack habits.
传统上，他们可能只是询问人们的零食习惯。
In today's digital age, apps can ask customers to swipe right on the flavours they fancy.
在当今的数字时代，应用程序可以要求顾客向右滑动已选择自己喜欢的口味。
Companies can search the internet for every restaurant menu in a specific market, looking out for the latest taste trends and in-demand ingredients.
公司可以在互联网上搜索特定市场的每一份餐厅菜单，留意最新的口味趋势和受欢迎的食材。
Snack trends also change over time.
零食趋势也随时间而变化。
When British supermarkets were encouraged to remove unhealthy snacks from the shelves next to where people queue up, companies were quick to provide healthier treats.
当英国超市被鼓励从人们排队买单旁边的货架上撤走不健康的零食时，公司迅速提供了更健康的零食。
They can also reflect different histories of migration.
它们也能反映不同的移民历史。
One British snack company found that flavours common in South Asian cuisine sold well in the UK, but less so in the US, where there is less of a tradition of Indian food.
一家英国零食公司发现，南亚菜肴中常见的口味在英国卖得很好，但在美国就不那么好了，因为那里很少爱吃印度食品的传统。
And demand for more sustainability has led some entrepreneurs to experiment with using insects as an alternative source of protein for snacks.
对可持续发展的需求促使一些企业家尝试用昆虫作为零食的替代蛋白质来源。
Other brands market themselves as offering a fairer price to the producers of the raw ingredients.
其他品牌则宣传自己为原料生产者提供更公平的价格（比如标榜自己选择更贵的有机食品）。
Of course, what might seem like the perfect idea might not actually be that practical.
当然，看似完美的想法实际上可能并不那么实用。
Ingredients that work well in a restaurant, might not work on a biscuit or crisp.
在餐厅里受欢迎的食材，放在饼干或薯片上可能就行不通。
Snacks that contain a lot of fresh ingredients may have too short a shelf life to be a viable product.
含有大量新鲜食材的零食可能保质期太短，无法成为真正可行的产品。
Some designs might need expensive packaging to protect them, which stops them being profitable.
有些设计可能需要昂贵的包装来保护它们，这使它们无法盈利。
There are many factors that influence our snacks.
影响我们零食的因素有很多。
Those that are successful reflect our tastes and concerns but can be limited by the manufacturing process.
成功的零食反映了我们的口味和关注点，但可能会受到制造过程的限制。